Guide to the Philip K. Bondy, Professor of Medicine, School of Medicine, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Philip K. Bond, professor of medicine, School of Medicine, Yale University, records
1947-1988
RU 962
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.02
(2 boxes and 1 folder)
The records consist of files of Philip K. Bondy, professor in the Yale School of Medicine, concerning the Department of Internal Medicine; Yale's relation to the Veteran's Administration Hospital in West Haven, Connecticut; and other administrative matters.
Bondy, Philip K. (Philip Kramer), 1917-2013
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 27-E (YRG 27-E), Records of departments, programs, and projects of the Yale School of Medicine.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of files of Philip K. Bondy, professor in the Yale School of Medicine, concerning the Department of Internal Medicine; Yale's relation to the Veteran's Administration Hospital in West Haven, Connecticut; and other administrative matters.
Universities and colleges -- Departments; Bondy, Philip K. (Philip Kramer), 1917-2013; Yale University. Department of Internal Medicine; Yale University. School of Medicine
- Philip K. Bondy correspondence, 1947-1964; Accession 19ND-A-500 (Box 1–2)
  - A-E, 1957-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abelson, 1955-1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Beckman, 1955-1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Farrand Co., 1955-1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Etiocholanolone Fever, 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - F-I, 1952-1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GP, 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Grace-New Haven Hospital, 1957-1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lilly, 1950-1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Merck, 1948-1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Parenzyme, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Pending, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Perkin-Elmer, 1955-1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Smith Kline and French, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine, 1951-1963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - T-Z, 1955-1964 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Upjohn, 1947-1956 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Veteran's Administration, 1946-1964 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Waterbury, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Yale, 1947-1964 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - American College of Physicians, 1950-1963 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - American Federation for Clinical Research, 1947-1953 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - American National Red Cross, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Armour, 1950-1956 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Association of American Physicians, 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Connecticut Diabetes Association, 1954-1956 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Connecticut Medical Service (CMS), 1952 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Connecticut Medical Society, 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Connecticut Medicine, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Diet Committee, New Haven Hospital, 1955-1958 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Endo Laboratories, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Frank W. Harris Ltd., 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Harrison: Principles of Internal Medicine, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - J-N, 1950-1964 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Laurentian Hormone Conference, 1950-1961 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Lectures, 1958-1963 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Lilly, 1949-1956 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Manitius, 1958-1962 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Metabolism Clinic, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Michael Reese Hospital, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1947-1958 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - O-S, 1951-1964 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Peterson, Undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Pharmaceuticals, 1950-1958 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Schering, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Smith Kline & French, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- School of Medicine. Philip K. Bondy records, 1971-1988; Accession 2005-A-040 (Box 1)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2063.
  Scope and Contents
  No inventory available.